Gentlemen, gentlemen.
Buy a newspaper!
Breaking news!
Big news from Lijia Town last night!
Mengzhu is dead.
Benefactor Li's bloodline might end here.
How did she die?
I know about this.
At the Li Mansion...
The living occupy it by day,
and ghosts take over by night.
Master Li had three wives in succession.
They all died mysteriously.
Later on, I heard
their wronged spirits haunt Li Mansion.
They appear as soon as night falls.
Run!
The First Wife is back!
Then how exactly
did they die?
The First Wife died suddenly.
Madam!
Somebody, help!
The Second Wife
was killed by a falling chandelier.
The Second Wife is dead!
The Third Wife fell suddenly ill
and died as if possessed.
Hurry, save her!
And now, his daughter is dead,
Mengzhu.
All four of them
were claimed by a vengeful spirit.
Who is Jiang Huai?
I am.
So you're Jiang Huai.
Jiang Huai is exactly who our lady wants.
Grab him!
Your lady?
Kidnapping someone in broad daylight?
What are you doing?
Get out of the way!
Stop it!
Let my master go!
Let me go!
Let go! Scram!
Why are you hitting people?
Our lady is having a ghost marriage.
You're the one our lady fancies.
Come with us!
Move! It's time for a ghost marriage.
Hurry up!
Let my master go!
I don't even know you guys!
- Master! - Move!
Wh-what are you doing?
Enough.
Is there no law here?
The law?
Half of this Lijia Town
was funded and built by Benefactor Li.
Around here,
Benefactor Li is the law.
Ghost marriage?
How does that work?
Finding a spouse for the deceased.
Simply put,
they'll take the couple
and bury them together in one coffin.
As for you,
during the holidays from now on,
burn extra paper money for your master.
Master!
You...
Detective!
Something happened to my master!
You have to save him!
Isn't your master incredibly capable?
He made the gold shop robbery into a story
and made you tell it.
Now look,
the whole town knows about the case.
Please, Detective!
You have to save my master!
Benefactor Li took him for a ghost marriage.
He'll be buried with a dead person!
Wait, wait.
What... what ghost marriage?
If you just save my master,
I'll work like a horse to repay you!
- Please, Detective! - Alright, alright!
- I promise you. - Please save my master!
I promise you.
I'll save your master.
Where is he?
Just you?
They're skilled fighters.
Shouldn't you get some backup?
No need.
I'm more than enough.
Back in school,
I was the kickboxing champion.
That's enough.
Let's go.
It's just like Master said.
She's not well-liked.
She doesn't even have a single officer.
My lady...
Why did you have to leave so soon?
Chunmei didn't even get to see you marry.
When you reach the underworld,
don't cross the Bridge of Helplessness yet.
Wait for your groom, Jiang Huai.
Move!
Your grand wedding is tonight.
Behave yourself!
My lady,
Didn't you love Jiang Huai's storytelling?
He'll be there to keep you company soon.
Move!
Keep moving!
What are you looking at? Move it!
Move! Move!
My lady!
Stop yelling! Hurry up!
What are you looking at?
Keep moving! Move it!
Move!
Hurry up!
Guard the door.
Don't let anyone in.
Got it.
Get back to work.
Move. We can't miss the auspicious hour.
Hurry up!
Behave!
Kneel!
Mengzhu of the Li Mansion died young.
In life, she admired scholar Jiang Huai.
To fulfill Mengzhu's dying wish,
May Mengzhu, on the road to the underworld,
have a husband by her side,
and no longer be lonely.
Here.
Bury this with Mengzhu in her coffin.
Heavenly Craftsmanship.
How did it end up in his hands?
The Wenchang Pavilion in our family library
holds over 13,000 ancient books.
Especially this one.
The sole surviving Ming Dynasty copy,
Heavenly Craftsmanship.
It records over 300 crafting methods,
and is a priceless treasure of Chinese crafting.
You must protect this book well.
When the situation stabilizes,
print more copies of it.
Popularize these crafting methods
so our ancestors' wisdom endures forever.
Yes, Father.
The lifeblood of our Jiang family
is this book, Heavenly Craftsmanship.
Remember.
As long as you live,
the book must survive.
Huai, run!
Run!
Could they have come back again?
Master, don't be afraid.
As long as Eldest Miss is buried in time,
this disaster will be quelled.
Eldest Miss must be buried tonight.
Heaven and Earth witness the soul's return.
Yin and Yang in harmony, forever at peace.
The ghost marriage wine seals this union.
Li Mengzhu and Jiang Huai are now wed.
Escort them to the mourning hall!
A ghost!
A ghost! Run!
They've come back!
A ghost!
Husband